{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962430281","data":{"timestamp":" 946962430281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962439223","data":{"timestamp":" 946962439222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962439458","data":{"timestamp":" 946962439458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962440430","data":{"timestamp":" 946962440430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962441716","data":{"timestamp":" 946962441715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962444649","data":{"timestamp":" 946962444649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962445506","data":{"timestamp":" 946962445505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962445828","data":{"timestamp":" 946962445827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962447071","data":{"timestamp":" 946962447071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962450670","data":{"timestamp":" 946962450669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962451664","data":{"timestamp":" 946962451663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962451928","data":{"timestamp":" 946962451928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962452884","data":{"timestamp":" 946962452884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962455815","data":{"timestamp":" 946962455815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962456859","data":{"timestamp":" 946962456859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962457339","data":{"timestamp":" 946962457338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962461905","data":{"timestamp":" 946962461904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962462006","data":{"timestamp":" 946962462005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 7c1c57a0-53a1-47ff-87af-6fbabbc7ba81"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962548359","data":{"timestamp":" 946962548359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962548976","data":{"timestamp":" 946962548975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962549201","data":{"timestamp":" 946962549201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962549795","data":{"timestamp":" 946962549795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962550559","data":{"timestamp":" 946962550559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962551543","data":{"timestamp":" 946962551542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962552177","data":{"timestamp":" 946962552177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962553354","data":{"timestamp":" 946962553354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962554095","data":{"timestamp":" 946962554095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962555328","data":{"timestamp":" 946962555328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962556141","data":{"timestamp":" 946962556140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962556628","data":{"timestamp":" 946962556628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962557543","data":{"timestamp":" 946962557543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962563185","data":{"timestamp":" 946962563185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962565608","data":{"timestamp":" 946962565608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962567899","data":{"timestamp":" 946962567899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962569972","data":{"timestamp":" 946962569971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962572113","data":{"timestamp":" 946962572113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962576185","data":{"timestamp":" 946962576185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962578734","data":{"timestamp":" 946962578734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962581456","data":{"timestamp":" 946962581455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962583962","data":{"timestamp":" 946962583962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962586132","data":{"timestamp":" 946962586132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962588707","data":{"timestamp":" 946962588706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962592407","data":{"timestamp":" 946962592407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962594416","data":{"timestamp":" 946962594416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962596159","data":{"timestamp":" 946962596159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962596241","data":{"timestamp":" 946962596241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962602930","data":{"timestamp":" 946962602930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962609510","data":{"timestamp":" 946962609510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962615689","data":{"timestamp":" 946962615689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 78b1ed03-ca78-4969-b8c2-5e63323553d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962650579","data":{"timestamp":" 946962650579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ovy_"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962666661","data":{"timestamp":" 946962666661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niny_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962676741","data":{"timestamp":" 946962676740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niny_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962687758","data":{"timestamp":" 946962687758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niny_"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962701026","data":{"timestamp":" 946962701026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jan_"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962710664","data":{"timestamp":" 946962710664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tam_"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962721079","data":{"timestamp":" 946962721079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wang_"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962729483","data":{"timestamp":" 946962729483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wa_"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962747188","data":{"timestamp":" 946962747188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mamb_"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962759238","data":{"timestamp":" 946962759238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mamb_"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962768419","data":{"timestamp":" 946962768418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962790567","data":{"timestamp":" 946962790567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_bat_"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962803849","data":{"timestamp":" 946962803849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962812307","data":{"timestamp":" 946962812307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962821601","data":{"timestamp":" 946962821601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.5.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962830808","data":{"timestamp":" 946962830808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962840827","data":{"timestamp":" 946962840827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962850120","data":{"timestamp":" 946962850120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" f98e6932-b086-4aa2-97cf-0d68abdae91e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.5.fin.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_rel_"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962880241","data":{"timestamp":" 946962880241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1ba3e5d2-0b27-4359-a09d-ca27e9a4093b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962880464","data":{"timestamp":" 946962880464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1ba3e5d2-0b27-4359-a09d-ca27e9a4093b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962880676","data":{"timestamp":" 946962880676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1ba3e5d2-0b27-4359-a09d-ca27e9a4093b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962880747","data":{"timestamp":" 946962880747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1ba3e5d2-0b27-4359-a09d-ca27e9a4093b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962901651","data":{"timestamp":" 946962901651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_myembamba_myembamba-alikutana-waliuliza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" myembamba"," userResponse":" waliuliza"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962908597","data":{"timestamp":" 946962908597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_myembamba_myembamba-alikutana-waliuliza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" myembamba"," userResponse":" myembamba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962914502","data":{"timestamp":" 946962914502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akamwomba_akamwomba-akitembea-hangeweza"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akamwomba"," userResponse":" akamwomba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962921334","data":{"timestamp":" 946962921333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanamume_mwanamume-akamwabia-alikutana"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanamume"," userResponse":" mwanamume"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962928073","data":{"timestamp":" 946962928073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akaondoka_jinyonyoe-akaondoka-kukanyaga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akaondoka"," userResponse":" akaondoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962939614","data":{"timestamp":" 946962939614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_najiuliza_alipofika-najiuliza-wanaokuja"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" najiuliza"," userResponse":" najiuliza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962945025","data":{"timestamp":" 946962945024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nilifanya_nilifanya-wakafanya-alifurahi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nilifanya"," userResponse":" nilifanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962950319","data":{"timestamp":" 946962950319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kupendeza_kupendeza-tafadhali-alifungua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kupendeza"," userResponse":" kupendeza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962957191","data":{"timestamp":" 946962957191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walisikia_alifikiri-kujificha-walisikia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walisikia"," userResponse":" walisikia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962964599","data":{"timestamp":" 946962964599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alikimbia_akakubali-alikimbia-mashuhuri"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alikimbia"," userResponse":" alikimbia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962972582","data":{"timestamp":" 946962972582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alipokuwa_boda boda-alipokuwa-wakicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alipokuwa"," userResponse":" alipokuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962978333","data":{"timestamp":" 946962978332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_alipokuwa_boda boda-alipokuwa-wakicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946962988006","data":{"timestamp":" 946962988005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" e41b8b40-3295-4895-a17b-73f13ab6150c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.9.lc.rand.stat.noShow.12__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alipokuwa_boda boda-alipokuwa-wakicheza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963002888","data":{"timestamp":" 946963002888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963010489","data":{"timestamp":" 946963010489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963018679","data":{"timestamp":" 946963018678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963026786","data":{"timestamp":" 946963026786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963034519","data":{"timestamp":" 946963034519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963035097","data":{"timestamp":" 946963035097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963041366","data":{"timestamp":" 946963041366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963048649","data":{"timestamp":" 946963048649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963049562","data":{"timestamp":" 946963049562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963054606","data":{"timestamp":" 946963054606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963064233","data":{"timestamp":" 946963064233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963073845","data":{"timestamp":" 946963073845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963082187","data":{"timestamp":" 946963082187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963088321","data":{"timestamp":" 946963088321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963097826","data":{"timestamp":" 946963097826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963105260","data":{"timestamp":" 946963105260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 10136c70-6704-4048-a8a6-cb830a3d1fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963131852","data":{"timestamp":" 946963131852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_waligundua_waligundua-wakitembea-aliniuliza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" waligundua"," userResponse":" waligundua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963139503","data":{"timestamp":" 946963139503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimweleza_akakumbuka-alimweleza-kingetokea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimweleza"," userResponse":" alimweleza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963146636","data":{"timestamp":" 946963146636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alinguruma_walimsikia-angekubali-alinguruma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alinguruma"," userResponse":" alinguruma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963155490","data":{"timestamp":" 946963155490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimuuliza_kuwasaidia-alimwuliza-alimuuliza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimuuliza"," userResponse":" alimwuliza"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963165954","data":{"timestamp":" 946963165954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimuuliza_kuwasaidia-alimwuliza-alimuuliza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimuuliza"," userResponse":" alimuuliza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963173195","data":{"timestamp":" 946963173195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alichotaka_alichotaka-alimuuliza-walimfuata"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alichotaka"," userResponse":" alichotaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963178783","data":{"timestamp":" 946963178783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aliufungua_aliufungua-kuwapeleka-uliangusha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aliufungua"," userResponse":" aliufungua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963192384","data":{"timestamp":" 946963192384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alijificha_alijificha-aliyemtaka-alichotaka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alijificha"," userResponse":" alijificha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963214672","data":{"timestamp":" 946963214672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawakutaka_nimpendaye-hawakutaka-alichotaka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawakutaka"," userResponse":" alichotaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963221936","data":{"timestamp":" 946963221936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawakutaka_nimpendaye-hawakutaka-alichotaka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawakutaka"," userResponse":" hawakutaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963230248","data":{"timestamp":" 946963230247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ningependa_kingetokea-alinguruma-ningependa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ningependa"," userResponse":" ningependa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963237657","data":{"timestamp":" 946963237657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukimbilia_alishindwa-alikumbuka-kukimbilia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukimbilia"," userResponse":" kukimbilia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963241413","data":{"timestamp":" 946963241413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 9db1c663-8ad2-4cbe-bd38-434168a84093"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.10.lc.rand.stat.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kukimbilia_alishindwa-alikumbuka-kukimbilia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963252407","data":{"timestamp":" 946963252407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963252630","data":{"timestamp":" 946963252630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963253593","data":{"timestamp":" 946963253593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963254866","data":{"timestamp":" 946963254866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963257726","data":{"timestamp":" 946963257726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963258570","data":{"timestamp":" 946963258570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963258886","data":{"timestamp":" 946963258886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963260123","data":{"timestamp":" 946963260122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963263714","data":{"timestamp":" 946963263714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963264697","data":{"timestamp":" 946963264697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963264950","data":{"timestamp":" 946963264950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963265429","data":{"timestamp":" 946963265428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963265513","data":{"timestamp":" 946963265513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 810ce7b0-7bf8-49b9-8ee9-930bcb1d9f38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963287405","data":{"timestamp":" 946963287404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_walimfuata_kukasirike_alimpeleka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963294058","data":{"timestamp":" 946963294058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ukiangalia_wakatoroka_nikikuokoa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963300736","data":{"timestamp":" 946963300736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumfagilia_kuwafukuza_niliyoweka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963307401","data":{"timestamp":" 946963307401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ningevivaa_kukosolewa_aliofunzwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963314032","data":{"timestamp":" 946963314032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_aliniwekea_limezimika_unavipenda"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963320681","data":{"timestamp":" 946963320680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amefunikwa_nimeugonga_nilifurahi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963327295","data":{"timestamp":" 946963327295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililoitwa_ukishirika_alimwarifu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963333907","data":{"timestamp":" 946963333907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akimpeleka_kilichooza_tunayovuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963340543","data":{"timestamp":" 946963340542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wanakijiji_walitambua_vimepasuka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963347204","data":{"timestamp":" 946963347204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tutatembea_akionyesha_ameonyesha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.10.noShow.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963360384","data":{"timestamp":" 946963360384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_080658"," gameId":" 1340102c-5796-4d18-ac09-eec150d1620e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.10.noShow.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_tutatembea_akionyesha_ameonyesha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}